Howard Teichmann Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
Howard Teichmann Papers 1857-2001 1940-1987
MSS84881
Teichmann, Howard, 1916-1987
49,500 items
141 containers plus 13 oversize
60 linear feet
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Author, educator, and theater administrator. Correspondence, drafts and typescripts of writings, financial records, notes, photographs, and research material pertaining to Teichmann's career as a playwright, biographer, educator, and theater administrator.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Abbott, George, 1887-1995--Correspondence.; Coca, Imogene--Correspondence.; Fonda, Henry, 1905-1982.; Hayes, Helen, 1900-1993--Correspondence.; Houseman, John, 1902-1988--Correspondence.; Kaufman, George S. (George Simon), 1889-1961--Correspondence.; Kaufman, George S. (George Simon), 1889-1961.; Kroll, Lucy--Correspondence.; Longworth, Alice Roosevelt, 1884-1980.; Prince, Harold, 1928-2019--Correspondence.; Schary, Dore--Correspondence.; Shubert, Milton.; Stevens, Roger L.--Correspondence.; Styne, Jule, 1905-1994--Correspondence.; Sulzberger, Iphigene Ochs--Correspondence.; Teichmann, Evelyn Goldstein.; Teichmann, Howard.; Teichmann, Howard. Alice: The life and times of Alice Roosevelt Longworth. 1979.; Teichmann, Howard. Fonda: My life as told to Howard Teichmann. 1981.; Teichmann, Howard. George S. Kaufman: An intimate portrait. 1972.; Teichmann, Howard. Smart aleck: The wit, world, and life of Alexander Woollcott. 1976.; Wilson, Earl, 1907- --Correspondence.; Woollcott, Alexander, 1887-1943.
Organizations
Barnard College--Faculty.; Columbia Broadcasting System, inc.; Dramatists Guild.; National Broadcasting Company.; Shubert Theatre Enterprises.; United States. Navy Department.; United States. Office of War Information.; University of Wisconsin--Students.
Subjects
Actors--Biography.; American drama.; Authors--Biography.; Children of presidents--United States--Biography.; Dramatists, American--Biography.; Radio programs.; Radio scripts.; Television.; World War, 1939-1945.
Places
United States--Biography.
Occupations
Administrators.; Authors.; Educators.
Acquisition Information
The papers of Howard Teichmann, author, educator, and theater administrator, were given to the Library of Congress between 2002 and 2006 by his wife, Evelyn Teichmann, and his daughter, Judith Teichmann Steckler.
Transfers
Items have been transferred from the Manuscript Division to other custodial divisions of the Library. A book, playbills, and play editions of scripts have been transferred to the Music Division. Audiotapes, videotapes, and disk recordings have been transferred to the Motion Picture, Broadcasting, and Recorded Sound Division. Some periodicals have been transferred to the Serial and Government Publications Division. Show cards have been to the Prints and Photographs Division. All transfers are identified in these divisions as part of the Howard Teichmann papers.
Related Materials
Related collections in the Library of Congress are the Lucy Kroll Papers in the Manuscript Division and the George S. Kaufman Collection in the Manuscript Division. Additional material can be found in the Howard Teichmann Papers at the State Historical Society of Wisconsin, Madison.
Access and Restrictions
The papers of Howard Teichmann are open to research. Researchers are advised to contact the Manuscript Reading Room prior to visiting. Many collections are stored off-site and advance notice is needed to retrieve these items for research use.
Biographical Note
Date Event
1916, Jan. 22 Born, Chicago, Ill.
1938 B.A., University of Wisconsin, Madison, Wis. Stage manager and assistant to the president, Mercury Theatre on the Air
1939 Married Evelyn Goldstein
1939 1953 Writer, director, and producer of radio and television programs
1942 1943 Senior editor, United States Office of War Information, overseas branch
1943 1945 Radio consultant to Lieutenant General Brehon Summerville, United States Army
1946 1986 Professor of English, Barnard College, Columbia University, New York, N.Y.
1953 Coauthored with George S. Kaufman, The Solid Gold Cadillac (play)
1953 1987 Served on council and several committees, Dramatists Guild
1957 Published Miss Lonelyhearts (play)
1958 Published The Girls in 509 (play)
1960 Published Julia, Jake, and Uncle Joe (play)
1962 1972 Executive vice president, Shubert Theatres Enterprises
1963 Published A Rainy Day in Newark (play)
1972 Published George S. Kaufman: An Intimate Portrait. New York: Atheneum
1976 Published Smart Aleck: The Wit, World, and Life of Alexander Woollcott. New York: William Morrow
1979 Published Alice: The Life and Times of Alice Roosevelt Longworth. New York: Prentice-Hall Published and directed Smart Aleck (play)
1981 Published Fonda: My Life as Told to Howard Teichmann. New York: New American Library
1987, July 7 Died, New York, N.Y.
Scope and Content Note
The papers of Howard Teichmann (1916-1987) span the years 1857-2001, with the bulk of the items concentrated in the period from 1940 to 1987. The collection contains appointment calendars, contracts, correspondence, financial records, notes, printed matter, and writings pertaining to Teichmann's personal life and career as an author, educator, and theater administrator. It is arranged in six series: Correspondence, Personal File, Organizations File, Writings File, Miscellany, and Oversize.
The Correspondence series contains letters received and copies of letters sent by Teichmann. Notable correspondents include George Abbott, Imogene Coca, Helen Hayes, John Houseman, Lucy Kroll, Harold Prince, Dore Schary, Roger L. Stevens, Jule Styne, Iphigene Ochs Sulzberger, and Earl Wilson. Teichmann's correspondence with George S. Kaufman is located in the background information pertaining to the book George S Kaufman: An Intimate Portrait.
The Personal File consists primarily of family correspondence, estate and financial records, and household, medical, and travel papers. Contracts and account books pertain to a partnership agreement between Teichmann and his wife Evelyn Goldstein Teichmann. Teichmann's leadership role in his apartment association is also documented.
The Organizations File reflects Teichmann's involvement in professional and cultural institutions including his student and alumni activities with the University of Wisconsin at Madison, his teaching career at Barnard College, his leadership positions in the Dramatists Guild, and his employment by the several Shubert theater companies. It also contains his work for the United States Office of War Information during World War II.
The Writings File consists of articles for magazines and newspapers, books, films, plays, radio programs, short stories, speeches, and television programs. Each genre contains material pertaining to the production and performance of the work. Teichmann's published books consist of his biographies of Henry Fonda, George S. Kaufman, Alice Roosevelt Longworth, and Alexander Woollcott. Each book includes typescripts of interviews with the subjects' colleagues and family members. Among his unpublished books is a work originally focused on John Shubert, The Man In The Blue Serge Suit, but later expanded to include other members of the Shubert family theater empire. Most notable among the plays is Teichmann's collaboration with George S. Kaufman on The Solid Gold Cadillac. The radio section reflects Teichmann's work with programs such as Ford Theatre and Orson Welles' Mercury Theatre on the Air as well as numerous “soap operas.” He also worked for the television networks Columbia Broadcasting System and National Broadcasting Company.
The Miscellany series contains notes and notebooks regarding personal subjects intermingled with professional and creative material. There is also a section pertaining to Milton Shubert's work for the United States Navy Department during World War II.
Related collections in the Library of Congress are the Lucy Kroll Papers in the Manuscript Division and the George S. Kaufman Collection in the Music Division. Additional material can be found in the Howard Teichmann Papers at the State Historical Society of Wisconsin, Madison.
Organization of the Papers
The collection is arranged in six series:
Correspondence, 1938-2000
Personal File, 1932-2001
Organizations File, 1905-1999
Writings File, 1857-1996
Miscellany, 1941-1987
Oversize, 1905-1982
Container List
- Correspondence, 1938-2000 (Box 1-17)
  Letters sent and received by Teichmann.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1938-1947, (9 folders) (Box 1)
  - 1948-1955, (9 folders) (Box 2)
  - 1956
    - Jan.-Apr.
    - May-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 3)
  - 1957-1959, (5 folders)
  - 1960
    - Jan.-July, (2 folders)
    - Aug.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 4)
  - 1961-1963, (6 folders)
  - 1964-1967, (5 folders) (Box 5)
  - 1968
    - Jan.-July, (2 folders)
    - Aug.-Dec. (Box 6)
  - 1969-1971, (5 folders)
  - 1972
    - Jan.-May
    - June-Dec., (6 folders) (Box 7)
  - 1973
    - Jan.-Feb.
    - Mar.-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 8)
  - 1974, (2 folders)
  - 1975
    - Jan.-June
    - July-Dec. (Box 9)
  - 1976
    - Jan.-Aug., (6 folders)
    - Sept.-Dec. (Box 10)
  - 1977-1978, (4 folders)
  - 1979
    - Jan.-Aug., (2 folders)
    - Sept.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 11)
  - 1980, (2 folders)
  - 1981
    - Jan.-Aug.
    - Sept.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - 1982, (4 folders)
  - 1983-1985, (6 folders) (Box 13)
  - 1986
    - Jan.-June
    - July-Dec. (Box 14)
  - 1987-2000, (6 folders)
  - Undated, (1 folder); (6 folders); (4 folders) (Box 15, Box 16, Box 17)
- Personal File, 1932-2001 (Box 18-31)
  Address books, appointment calendars, awards, biographical information, family correspondence, financial records, household papers, and photographs.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material and therein chronologically.
  - Address books, undated, (3 folders) (Box 18)
  - Appointment calendars
    - 1954-1955, (3 folders)
    - 1956-1960, (5 folders) (Box 19)
    - 1961-1964, (4 folders) (Box 20)
    - 1965-1971, (3 folders) (Box 21)
    - 1972-1976, (3 folders) (Box 22)
    - 1977-1982, (3 folders) (Box 23)
    - 1983-1987, (3 folders) (Box 24)
  - Awards and certificates, 1934, 1945, 1964, 1980-1984 (Box 25)
  - Baylek v. Baylek, 1951-1952, (2 folders)
  - Biographical information, 1934-1989, undated, (3 folders)
  - Christmas card lists
    - 1941-1956, (2 folders)
    - 1957-1962, undated (Box 26)
  - Correspondence
    - 1932-1986, (8 folders)
    - 1987-2001, (6 folders) (Box 27)
    - Undated, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 28)
  - Estate papers, 1967, 1974, 1987, 1993, undated
  - Financial records
    - Expenses and deposits, 1944, (4 folders)
    - Insurance, 1944-1949, 1956, 1967-1981, 1988
    - Investments
      - 1950-1956, (2 folders)
      - 1957-1971, 1981-1988, 1992-1995, (3 folders) (Box 29)
    - Taxes, 1941-1972, 1979-1985, (4 folders)
  - Household papers, 1939-1960, 1966-1994, undated, (5 folders)
  - Medical papers, 1976-1977, 1986, 1998
  - Miscellany, 1951-1952, 1967, 1973-1982, 1991, undated
  - Partnership agreement, 1946, 1982
  - Photographs, undated, (2 folders) (Box 30)
  - Residence association, 1942-1943, 1959-1987, undated, (8 folders)
  - Teichmann Productions, 1946-1974 See also Oversize
  - Travel papers, 1954-1982 (Box 31)
- Organizations File, 1905-1999 (Box 31-41)
  Contracts, correspondence, financial records, and printed matter pertaining to the professional and cultural organizations in which Teichmann participated.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of organization and therein chronologically.
  - Active Trading Co., 1973-1974 (Box 31)
  - Agency representation contracts, 1944-1946, 1953-1962, 1974-1978
  - American National Theatre and Academy, 1935, 1948-1951, 1964-1970, undated See also Containers 129-130, Theatre U.S.A. and Container 137, Showtime U.S.A., (5 folders)
  - Authors Guild, 1965-1983, undated
  - Authors League of America, 1942, 1947-1950, 1971, 1977-1981, undated, (2 folders)
  - Barnard College, New York, N.Y. (Box 32)
    - Appointment contracts, 1947-1985
    - Correspondence
      - 1946-1999, (8 folders)
      - Undated (Box 33)
    - Lectures, undated, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany, 1947-1948, 1956-1982, undated, (2 folders)
    - Printed matter, 1947-1987, undated, (3 folders)
  - Broadway Association, 1965-1973
  - Dramatists Guild
    - Concessions Committee, 1970-1980
    - Council, 1964-1972, undated, (3 folders) (Box 34)
    - Dramatists Guild Fund, 1962-1971, 1978-1987
    - Finance Committee, 1965-1982, undated, (4 folders)
    - Minimum basic agreements, 1949, 1955, 1965, 1972, undated, (2 folders)
    - Miscellany
      - 1945, 1964-1969, (2 folders)
      - 1970-1984, undated (Box 35)
  - Dramatists Play Service, 1956-1962, 1969, 1978-1986
  - Equity Theatre, 1965-1968
  - Hall of Fame for Great Americans, New York University, New York, N.Y., 1973, (2 folders)
  - Inner Circle, 1968
  - Lawrenceville School, Lawrenceville, N.J., 1965-1968, undated, (2 folders)
  - League of New York Theatres, 1968-1972, undated
  - Literary Guild, 1977
  - Shubert companies
    - Miscellany, 1972, undated
    - Sam S. Shubert Foundation
      - 1963-1969, (2 folders)
      - 1970-1985, undated, (3 folders) (Box 36)
    - Select Theatres, 1933, 1942, 1958-1977, undated, (7 folders)
    - Shubert Organization, 1970-1987
    - Shubert Theatres Enterprises
      - 1963-1965
      - 1966-1972, undated, (11 folders) (Box 37)
    - The Student Prince, 1966-1967 See Container 36, Select Theatres (Box 38)
    - Trebuhs Realty Co., 1972-1973
  - State Historical Society of Wisconsin, Madison, Wis., 1959-1987, undated, (4 folders)
  - Times Square Development Council, 1972, undated
  - United States Office of War Information
    - Background information
      - 167th anniversary of U. S. Marine Corps, 1942-1944, undated, (4 folders)
      - American Red Cross, 1945
      - Army Corps of Engineers, 1943, undated
      - Army Quartermaster Corps, 1941-1942
      - Army Signal Corps, 1942-1943, undated (Box 39)
      - Chemical warfare, 1942-1943, (2 folders)
      - Fact sheets and press releases, 1943-1945, undated
      - Infantry Journal, 1941-1942, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany
        - 1934, 1941-1943, (3 folders)
        - 1944, undated (Box 40)
      - Nazism and Germany, 1942-1943
      - Our Army Day by Day, 1941-1942, undated, (2 folders)
    - Correspondence, 1942-1945, undated, (2 folders)
  - University of Wisconsin, Madison, Wis.
    - Class work, 1936-1938, undated
    - Correspondence, 1941-1986, undated, (2 folders)
    - Directories, 1935-1942, (2 folders) (Box 41)
    - Haresfoot Club, 1905, 1935-1941, 1951-1963, undated See also Oversize, (4 folders)
    - Iron Cross Society, 1955-1956, 1978-1979
    - Miscellany, 1942-1946, 1959, 1967
  - WNYC-AM, FM, and TV, New York, N.Y., 1978-1986
- Writings File, 1857-1996 (Box 42-137)
  Background information, contracts, correspondence, drafts, financial records, notes, and printed matter relating to Teichmann's articles, books, plays, and radio and television programs.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of work and alphabetically therein by type of material.
  - Articles (Box 42)
    - Abbott, George, 1965, 1976, undated, (2 folders)
    - “Alice in Chicagoland,” 1979
    - “And a Hard Time Was Had by All,” 1958
    - “Be Kind to Critics?” 1961-1962
    - Book and theater reviews, 1951, 1972-1978, undated
    - “The Brave Journey of Helen Hayes,” 1985-1986, undated
    - “’Broadway' Is Not a Four Letter Word,” undated
    - “Broadway on the Road,” 1966
    - Coward, Noel, 1961
    - The Daily Cardinal, 1954
    - Fonda, Henry, 1981
    - “For Whom the Bell Rings—And Rings,” 1960
    - “G. S. K.,” undated
    - “Greeks Did Satire out of Meanness,” 1958
    - “Is It Mrs. Strasberg's Cooking?” 1962-1963
    - “ June Moon ,” 1973
    - Kaufman, George, 1967, undated
    - “The Man Who Hated Hollywood,” 1972
    - “The Man Who Refined the Wisecrack,” 1973
    - “Memories of a Legend,” 1981, undated (Box 43)
    - Miscellany, 1947, 1958-1980, undated
    - Morgan, Brewster, undated
    - “Myths of Present Day Playwriting,” 1961-1962
    - “O Pioneers!” 1959
    - “On Broadway,” (Earl Wilson column), 1966
    - “Poor Prophet,” 1982
    - Ticket brokers, 1968
    - Variety, 1961-1981
    - “What Happened to the Line ’It's a Nice Place to Visit?'” undated
    - “When a Playwright Writes a Flop,” 1957
    - “Why Can't Men Buy Clothes?” 1958
    - “You Can't Take It with You ,” 1979
  - Autobiography, undated, (2 folders)
  - Books
    - Proposed
      - “10 Words Or Less”
        - Correspondence, 1982
        - Notes, undated
        - Typescripts, 1978, (2 folders)
      - Barrymore, John, undated
      - “Battersea” (Box 44)
        - Drafts, undated
        - Notes, undated
        - Typescripts, undated, (6 folders) (Box 45)
      - Hayes, Helen
        - Background information
          - 1916-1923, 1935, 1942, 1980
          - Undated (Box 46)
        - Correspondence, 1980-1981, undated
        - Drafts, undated
      - “The Man in the Blue Serge Suit”
        - Background information
          - Interviews, 1991, undated, (3 folders)
          - Miscellany, 1948, undated
          - Newspaper clippings, 1905, 1939, 1953-1974, undated, (2 folders)
          - Notes, undated
        - Contracts, 1985-1987 (Box 47)
        - Correspondence, 1961, 1985-1988, undated, (2 folders)
        - Drafts
          - Early version, undated, (6 folders)
          - Miscellaneous pages, undated, (3 folders) (Box 48)
          - Typescripts, undated, (7 folders); (3 folders) (Box 49)
        - Miscellany, 1984
        - Notes, 1985, undated, (3 folders)
        - Photographs, undated, (2 folders) (Box 50)
      - Untitled, undated
    - Published
      - Alice: The Life and Times of Alice Roosevelt Longworth
        - Background information
          - Interviews, 1977-1978, (3 folders)
          - Miscellany, 1857, 1866-1876, 1945-1952, 1969-1978, undated, (2 folders)
          - Newspaper clippings
            - 1904-1909, 1918-1938
            - 1941-1944, 1950-1979, undated, (2 folders) (Box 51)
        - Contracts, 1977, undated
        - Correspondence, 1976-1988, undated, (3 folders)
        - Drafts
          - Bibliography and notes, undated, (2 folders)
          - Early version, undated, (2 folders); (4 folders) (Box 52)
          - Corrected typescript, undated, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 53)
          - Evelyn Teichmann's copy, undated, (4 folders)
          - Final typescript, undated, (2 folders) (Box 54)
          - Miscellaneous pages, undated
        - Notes, 1976, undated, (2 folders)
        - Permissions, 1979-1983
        - Photographs, 1932-1969, 1976-1978, undated, (3 folders)
        - Proofs, 1979, (1 folder) (Box 55)
        - Publicity, 1961, 1979-1980
        - Reviews, 1979-1980, (3 folders)
        - Royalty statements, 1977-1990
      - Fonda: My Life as Told to Howard Teichmann
        - Background information
          - Interviews, 1980-1981, undated
            - A-E, (2 folders)
            - F, (7 folders); (6 folders) (Box 56, Box 57, Box 58)
            - G
            - H-W, (10 folders) (Box 59)
          - Miscellany, 1975-1981, undated (Box 60)
          - Newspaper clippings, 1927, 1934-1982, undated, (3 folders)
          - Photocopied family letters, 1916, 1943, 1950, 1957, 1974-1980, undated, (2 folders)
          - Printed matter, 1952, 1979-1982, (3 folders)
        - Contracts, 1980
        - Correspondence
          - 1974-1979
          - 1980-1985, 1991, undated, (4 folders) (Box 61)
        - Drafts
          - Early version, undated, (5 folders); (8 folders); (3 folders) (Box 62, Box 63)
          - Typescripts, undated, (4 folders); (8 folders); (6 folders) (Box 64, Box 65)
        - Dramatic and serial rights, 1980-1981
        - Foreign rights, 1981-1983
        - Miscellany, 1980-1986, undated
        - Notes
          - 1980-1981
          - Undated, (1 folder) (Box 66)
        - Permissions, 1981-1986
        - Photographs, 1934, 1954, undated See also Oversize, (2 folders)
        - Proofs, 1981, (2 folders); (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 67, Box 68)
        - Publicity, 1979-1983, undated See also Oversize, (5 folders)
        - Reviews, 1981-1982
        - Royalty statements, 1981-1992, undated, (2 folders)
      - George S. Kaufman: An Intimate Portrait
        - Background information
          - Interviews, 1961-1971
            - A
            - B-F, (7 folders) (Box 69)
            - G-M, (8 folders) (Box 70)
            - N-Z, (5 folders) (Box 71)
          - Kaufman correspondence
            - 1912, 1918, 1923-1959, 1967-1972, (3 folders)
            - Undated, (2 folders) (Box 72)
          - Miscellany, 1917-1932, 1944, 1953, 1960-1961, 1971-1972, undated
          - Newspaper clippings, 1928-1929, 1935-1937, 1945-1969, 1975-1976, 1983, undated, (2 folders)
          - Notes, 1965, undated, (2 folders)
        - Contracts, 1962, 1971-1977
        - Correspondence
          - 1940, 1949, 1962
          - 1963-1985, undated, (3 folders) (Box 73)
        - Drafts
          - Bibliography and index, undated, (2 folders)
          - Early version, undated, (3 folders); (8 folders) (Box 74)
          - Miscellaneous pages, undated, (6 folders) (Box 75)
          - Preface, undated
          - Typescripts, undated, (1 folder); (7 folders); (8 folders); (3 folders) (Box 76, Box 77, Box 78, Box 79)
        - Dramatic and film rights, 1955, 1975-1976, 1984-1985, undated
        - Foreign rights, 1972-1973, undated
        - Notes
          - 1962-1965, 1971-1972
          - Undated, (3 folders); (4 folders) (Box 80)
        - Permissions, 1971-1975, 1982-1988, undated
        - Photographs, 1913-1916, 1936-1948, 1954, 1972, undated, (2 folders) (Box 81)
        - Proofs
          - Foundry, undated
          - Page
            - 1972
            - Undated, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 82, Box 83)
          - Uncorrected, 1972
        - Publicity
          - 1962-1972, (4 folders)
          - 1973-1980, undated (Box 84)
        - Reviews, 1972-1974, undated, (2 folders)
        - Royalty statements, 1962, 1972-1975
      - Smart Aleck: The Wit, World, and Life of Alexander Woollcott
        - Background information
          - Interviews, 1972-1975, undated
            - A-L, (4 folders)
            - M-Z, (7 folders) (Box 85)
          - Miscellany, 1932, 1941, 1948, 1971, undated
          - Newspaper clippings
            - 1925-1939
            - 1940-1946, 1959, 1972-1976, undated (Box 86)
          - Notes, 1922, 1934, 1940-1946, 1965, 1973-1974, undated, (2 folders)
          - Photocopied letters and diary, 1898-1899, 1912, 1928-1945, 1958, undated, (3 folders)
        - Contracts, 1972-1976
        - Correspondence
          - 1945, 1959, 1971-1972
          - 1973-1981, undated, (3 folders) (Box 87)
        - Drafts
          - Miscellaneous pages, undated, (3 folders); (5 folders) (Box 88, Box 89)
          - Typescripts
            - 1974, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 90)
            - 1975, (4 folders)
            - 1976, (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 91)
            - Undated, (4 folders); (5 folders) (Box 92)
        - Notes, undated, (2 folders)
        - Permissions, 1973, 1985
        - Photographs, undated See also Oversize, (6 folders) (Box 93)
        - Proofs, 1976
        - Publicity, 1976-1982, (3 folders) (Box 94)
        - Reviews, 1976
        - Royalty statements, 1972-1986
  - Film
    - The Dancing Detective
      - Contracts and correspondence, 1946-1948
      - Drafts, undated
        - First
        - Working, (4 folders)
        - Revised (Box 95)
    - Dora Cooper, 1959